

MUHAMMAD ALI TAHIR

E: alikhk1210@gmail.com

P: 0316-4954309

A: Huma street Taj Bagh Scheme , Lahore , Pakistan

Nationality:

Pakistani

Date of Birth:

12/10/1999

SKILLS

Data analysis

Problem solving

Communication

Project management

Time management

Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint)

LANGUAGES

Urdu

Engilsh

HOBBIES

- Video games
- Sports (Cricket)
- Movies
- Traveling

PROFILE

Experienced with working in an office environment and know how to deal with the time pressure Experienced with simulation, modeling and animation for designing and Microsoft office. This employment will allow me to explore my hidden talents so that I can utilize them in the future.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's in Aircraft Maintenance engineering and Technology | University of Management and Technology , Lahore

Oct 2018

FSc (Pre- Engineering) | Punjab Groups of colleges, Lahore

Jan 2016 - Dec 2017

Matriculation (Computer Science) | Lahore Cantt Public High School , Lahore

Jan 2014 - Dec 2015

EXPERIENCE

Administration Internee | University of Management and Technology , Lahore

Jun 2019 - Oct 2019

- Communicated with management, team, and customers in a professional manner using a combination of emails, phone calls, instant messages, and face-to-face meetings.
- Adapted to workflow changes and implemented continuous process improvements to overcome obstacles.
- Devised and implemented improvements to reporting procedures.
- Responsible for the analysis, documentation, and reporting of management information.

Designer | Hobby Lobby, Lahore

Aug 2020 - Oct 2020

- Established rapport with customers, developing effective communication among levels of the store's management.
- Trained users on new software applications and policies, increasing productivity.
- Work with team and management to deliver exceptional production operations.
- Fulfilled information requests from clients and conducted internet-based research on special projects.

INTERNSHIPS

Trainee Engineer | Pakistan Aeronautical Complex, Kamra, Kamra

Sep 2021 - Oct 2021

- Quickly adapt to new environments and roles, able to learn new languages, tools, or methodologies quickly.
- Experience with multiple hardware and software platforms.
- Greet clients and ascertain what each client wants or needs.